<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:media="http://search.yahoo.com/mrss/"><category term="investing" label="r/investing"/><updated>2021-02-12T23:29:29+00:00</updated><icon>https://www.redditstatic.com/icon.png/</icon><id>/r/investing/.rss</id><link rel="self" href="https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/.rss" type="application/atom+xml" /><link rel="alternate" href="https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/" type="text/html" /><title>Lose money with friends!</title><entry><author><name>/u/MasterCookSwag</name><uri>https://www.reddit.com/user/MasterCookSwag</uri></author><category term="investing" label="r/investing"/><content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Alright everyone, it looks like we had pretty broad support in &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/cuuo6j/yooo_get_in_here_peeps_state_of_the_subreddit/&quot;&gt;this thread&lt;/a&gt; when it comes to cracking down on the hyper partisanship that&amp;#39;s been spilling out of the political subreddits to all corners of reddit. In this thread I&amp;#39;m going to lay out some formal guidelines for comments on political topics. Since this is so widespread I want to be clear here: this post is everyone&amp;#39;s formal warning. That means temporary or in some cases permanent bans are being handed out for people who violate said guidelines immediately. This is really the only way to deal wit this issue. I&amp;#39;m going to try to get automod to sticky applicable threads with this post as well. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;First lets address politics&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I want to note something first: we are absolutely enforcing higher posting standards for political threads. I think it&amp;#39;s entirely uncontroversial to point out that calling Warren Buffett an asshole doesn&amp;#39;t nearly stir up the anger that calling any given political figure an asshole will. Comments like that being upvoted quickly derail threads and drive the discussion away from investing. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;So here&amp;#39;s the simple guideline which I&amp;#39;ll expand on: you&amp;#39;re free to express your opinion so long as it&amp;#39;s tied to investing, you put effort in to it, and it&amp;#39;s civil.&lt;/strong&gt; We&amp;#39;re not here to stop the free flow of discussion or ideas but we are here to keep discussion surrounding investing and civil.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tied to investing:&lt;/strong&gt; this should be pretty straightforward but I&amp;#39;m laying it out here anyway. Investing encompasses markets, economic impacts, corporate profits, shifts in the yield curve, the federal reserve, taxes, potential government spending that may impact your portfolio. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Investing does not encompass immigration, personal lives of politicians, social issues, climate change(unless specifically within the context of impact to energy or similar), how you feel about a particular news organization&amp;#39;s potential biases, etc. If it&amp;#39;s not in the first list it&amp;#39;s probably not investing related. Making comments pertaining to non investment related politics only serves to drive the conversation off course and create a thread that is indistinguishable from one in a political subreddit. Driving conversation off topic in high level comments by bringing up politics in unrelated threads also falls in this category. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Effort:&lt;/strong&gt; no shitposts. If you&amp;#39;re not conveying a thought or analysis of a particular subject then it&amp;#39;s probably best to not post. Furthermore top level comments like &amp;quot;fuck my portfolio&amp;quot; don&amp;#39;t help keeping conversation on track. Lastly and most importantly anything that falls in to the political meme universe isn&amp;#39;t going to fly here. That means if you&amp;#39;re repeating something like TDS, MAGA, trade wars are good and easy to win, Pocahontas, orange man bad, any of the millions of nicknames for the president, very stable genius, any given childish spin on Democrat/republican(ex DemocRAT or Republitard), etc isn&amp;#39;t tolerated. These sorts of things only serve to agitate those on the opposite end of the political spectrum and create partisan arguments.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Your post should be something like &amp;quot;I disagree/agree with Trump here because [policy] will do XYZ which is good/bad for ABC and blah blah blah blah&amp;quot;. If you are unable to express an investment related position on a topic without insults and memes then you probably should just go to a political subreddit and comment there.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Special note here: conspiracy theories about politics and markets are not allowed. If you are going to imply criminal market manipulation or insider trading proof in the form of reporting or other documentation is necessary. This is not a place for baseless accusations derived from political leaning. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Civility:&lt;/strong&gt; so we already don&amp;#39;t allow personal attacks here. Generally speaking many people identify so closely with political parties and politicians that they react to political attacks the same way they will to personal attacks. I get it, people get worked up over politics. Translating that emotion to a post here only serves to have people with opposing views get similarly worked up. This isn&amp;#39;t an appropriate subreddit for that. We&amp;#39;re here to discuss investing. So any comment that would violate our personal attacks rule if you made it towards another user is prohibited against political parties or figures. &lt;a href=&quot;/r/investing&quot;&gt;/r/investing&lt;/a&gt; is not a platform for people to express their outrage towards politicians or political parties. There are tons of subreddits for that sort of thing. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;So now that the guidelines are made clear, here&amp;#39;s the consequences. In our observation the vast majority of people engaging in political attacks and low effort posts are not regular contributors. They tend to frequent political subreddits and engage in political attacks elsewhere. So we&amp;#39;re automatically handing out 30 day bans for violation of the above rules. If you feel like your ban was in error or unfair you can appeal in modmail but we&amp;#39;re not really inclined to reverse decisions if you aren&amp;#39;t already a regular contributor. For egregious offenses the ban may be 60 days or permanent. For overt racism, death threats against any public figure, or similar there is an automatic permanent ban. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Now Corporate vs Investment News&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;/u/crasymike&quot;&gt;/u/crasymike&lt;/a&gt; did an awesome job laying out the general guidelines here: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/b3ss3q/topics_being_removed_corporate_news_vs_investor/&quot;&gt;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/b3ss3q/topics_being_removed_corporate_news_vs_investor/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m going to just copy some of the hard guidelines here so they&amp;#39;re in the same place but take a look at that thread to see a full explanation.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;tl;dr Not all corporate news is investment news. If you post a topic the onus is on you to guide the discussion towards investing. If the moderators feel that a topic lacks relevance (which is more clearly defined below) then it might be removed. Off-topic top-level comments have similar standards applied to them.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;This means that the onus is on you as the person posting the topic to guide the discussion. As moderators all we can do is remove offending comments, but we can&amp;#39;t incite relevant discussion in every topic.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Tell us, why is this political news impactful? Seek out an article that discusses market impacts rather than a generic article. If you want to post corporate news then find an article that includes the impact on the investment. Copy that information into the body of your post. Include price history. Add other pertinent links or details for the corporate.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;If you include no relevant investing information then don&amp;#39;t be surprised if the topic is completely derailed from discussing investing. If you are posting a topic you need to invite people to talk about investing by using an article, or including information, that is pertinent to investors.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;As moderators, we have a few policies that we use to guide ourselves. This is a broad rule that requires some interpretation, but here we go:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;If we can&amp;#39;t figure out how your topic relates to investing, and the article doesn&amp;#39;t include any (or extremely little) market news, and the body of your post doesn&amp;#39;t link the topic to investing we will probably remove it as off-topic.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;If your topic has an indirect relation to investing (such as being about a public company, or is major market shifting news) but you included no market information and the article(s) you linked have no investing information we may remove it if we feel that there is no clear reason to expect on-topic comments.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;If someone posts a top-level comment on a thread that completely derails away from investing we will probably remove it.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;If the policies above would result in the modteam seemingly needing to remove nearly every top level comment in a thread, and we felt like your thread is &amp;quot;borderline&amp;quot; not investing news, then we will take this as confirmation that the topic wasn&amp;#39;t investing news. If the entire conversation in a thread is already driven off topic by political attacks or off topic discussion we will lock and remove a thread no matter how topical it is. Please do your part and downvote/report political attacks even if you agree with them. This will prevent us from just nuking a thread&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/user/MasterCookSwag&quot;&gt; /u/MasterCookSwag &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/cyee69/formal_posting_guidelines_for_political_topics/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/cyee69/formal_posting_guidelines_for_political_topics/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t3_cyee69</id><link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/cyee69/formal_posting_guidelines_for_political_topics/" /><updated>2019-09-01T19:31:28+00:00</updated><title>Formal posting guidelines for political topics and what constitutes investment vs corporate news. **READ BEFORE COMMENTING IN THIS SUB PLEASE**</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/AutoModerator</name><uri>https://www.reddit.com/user/AutoModerator</uri></author><category term="investing" label="r/investing"/><content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;If your question is &amp;quot;I have $10,000, what do I do?&amp;quot; or other &amp;quot;advice for my personal situation&amp;quot; questions, you should include relevant information, such as the following:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;How old are you? What country do you live in?&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Are you employed/making income? How much?&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;What are your objectives with this money? (Buy a house? Retirement savings?)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;What is your time horizon? Do you need this money next month? Next 20yrs?&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;What is your risk tolerance? (Do you mind risking it at blackjack or do you need to know its 100% safe?)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;What are you current holdings? (Do you already have exposure to specific funds and sectors? Any other assets?)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Any big debts (include interest rate) or expenses?&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;And any other relevant financial information will be useful to give you a proper answer.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;Please consider consulting our FAQ first - &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/wiki/faq&quot;&gt;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/wiki/faq&lt;/a&gt; And our &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/about/sidebar&quot;&gt;side bar&lt;/a&gt; also has useful resources. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Be aware that these answers are just opinions of Redditors and should be used as a starting point for your research. You should strongly consider seeing a registered financial rep before making any financial decisions!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/user/AutoModerator&quot;&gt; /u/AutoModerator &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/li82a3/daily_advice_thread_all_basic_help_or_advice/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/li82a3/daily_advice_thread_all_basic_help_or_advice/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t3_li82a3</id><link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/li82a3/daily_advice_thread_all_basic_help_or_advice/" /><updated>2021-02-12T10:00:14+00:00</updated><title>Daily Advice Thread - All basic help or advice questions must be posted here.</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/rareliquid</name><uri>https://www.reddit.com/user/rareliquid</uri></author><category term="investing" label="r/investing"/><content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hello! Wanted to share my thoughts on Palantir ahead of its earnings next TUESDAY (Edit: sorry I got the day wrong in the title but the date 2/16 is correct). Warning: long post ahead and TLDR at the bottom.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Palantir Business Overview&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;In one sentence, Palantir creates &lt;strong&gt;operating systems&lt;/strong&gt; that integrates vast amounts of data from an organization’s various data silos and allows users to build applications that drive better decision making&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;If that&amp;#39;s confusing, no worries. The way I like to think of Palantir&amp;#39;s software is that if Batman purchased the software from a company today for his supercomputer which aggregates data from thousands of sources and allows him to make intelligent decisions, that software would be from Palantir&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;The company has three main software platforms: &lt;strong&gt;Gotham, Foundry, and Apollo&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Gotham (government side)&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Gotham is Palantir’s software offering primarily for defense and intelligence sectors, AKA governments&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Gotham is an end-to-end operating system that collects data from hundreds to millions of different sources and combines them onto one platform so users can manage operations&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Gotham is quickly becoming the de facto data solution across many US federal agencies and rumor has it that it was the software that helped track down Osama Bin Laden in 2011&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Foundry (commercial side)&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Next up is Foundry, a platform that is geared towards the 6,000 businesses around the world with over $500 million in revenue&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Similar to Gotham, Foundry transforms the ways organizations operate by creating a central operating system for their data&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;For example, one of Palantir’s customers is Skywise, an aviation platform that has become the central operating system for the airline industry&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Apollo (underlying infrastructure)&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Apollo is the last piece of the Palantir puzzle, and you can think of it as the underlying infrastructure that Gotham and Foundry lie upon&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Apollo is a relatively new platform that Palantir introduced in order to more efficiently update the software that runs Gotham and Foundry, increasing the number of upgrades Palantir can manage across installations from an average of 20,000 per week in Q2 2019 to more than 41,000 per week in Q2 2020&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;The company has estimated its &lt;strong&gt;total addressable market as $119 billion,&lt;/strong&gt; of which $63 billion is for the government side while $56 billion is for commercial side&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Palantir Business Model&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Known as &lt;strong&gt;Forward Deployed Engineers or FDEs,&lt;/strong&gt; Palantir leverages their technical talent as support and sales as well and they are often sent to the front lines of the battlefield for Gotham or company for Foundry &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;I believe that this in particular is what helped Palantir create a competitive moat in the government sector&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;While the FDEs are a differentiator, Palantir has also started to build out a &lt;strong&gt;more traditional salesforce&lt;/strong&gt; in order to better target customers and explain the company’s value proposition but this salesforce currently only accounts for 3% of the company’s total headcount&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Using both FDEs and a traditional salesforce, Palantir’s business model employs a 3 step process: acquire, expand, and scale&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Acquire&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;In the acquire step, Palantir provides a potential customer with a short-term pilot program at Palantir’s expense and therefore operate at a loss&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Expand&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;In the expand phase, Palantir seeks to understand the customer’s key challenges and ensure that its software delivers results&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Scale&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;The scale phase is where Palantir thrives. At this point, the customer is essentially using Palantir’s software for its operations and Palantir can also upsell to the customer by continually offering new services with minimal extra cost&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;To give you a sense of the numbers for each phase, In 2019, Palantir generated a total of $742.6 million in revenue, of which &lt;strong&gt;$0.6 million&lt;/strong&gt; came from customers in the &lt;strong&gt;Acquire&lt;/strong&gt; phase, &lt;strong&gt;$176.3 million&lt;/strong&gt; from the &lt;strong&gt;Expand&lt;/strong&gt; phase, and &lt;strong&gt;$565.7&lt;/strong&gt; million from the &lt;strong&gt;Scale&lt;/strong&gt; phase&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Bull Case&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Section 2377&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;In 2016, Palantir sued the US Army in what’s known as Decision 2377&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;To go into the history a little bit, in 1994, the Federal Streamlining Acquisition Act (FASA) was passed, which required that the federal government consider and acquire readily available, proven commercial services like Palantir’s rather than custom-developed solutions built by the government which has a reputation for spending inefficiently&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;This rule was largely ignored until Palantir sued and won in court, and this was extremely important because it allowed Palantir to compete and win deals across all federal agencies, which greatly helps the company realize its total addressable market. Since then, Palantir&amp;#39;s revenue from the US Army and US government has skyrocketed&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Sticky, Best-in-Class Product&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Simply put, there is nothing that offers what Palantir is offering. Its technology is way beyond most of its competitors in terms of offering a premium operating system&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Palantir’s Gotham and Foundry often take more than a year to get fully up and running and the more it’s used, the more data in the system and the more time that has been spent by customers training employees on how to use the system&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Palantir’s platforms becomes incredibly expensive to switch out of not just in terms of money but also time, with customers saying replacing the system could take anywhere from 6 to 18 months&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;To further prove this point, Palantir’s top 20 customers have been with the company for an average of 7 years and as of October 2020, 93% of revenue was generated by existing customers&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;In addition to this, in the latest quarterly earnings, Palantir was selected out of 999 bids by the US Army for a 2-year $91 million contract to build AI and machine learning capabilities&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Positive Secular Trends and Growing, Achievable TAM&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;I think everyone at this point realizes that companies are going digital transformations and Palantir has spent $1.5 billion in the past 11 years creating innovative software that becomes increasingly powerful each day&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;The company is at the right place at the right time with a total addressable market expected to grow into the few hundreds of billions of dollars in the next 5 years&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;And with just about $1 billion dollars in revenue over the past 12 months, Palantir has less than 1% market share and has plenty of room for growth&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;But perhaps most importantly, Palantir is creating a much more efficient business model with an improving tech product that will help the company achieve its TAM &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;In the latest earnings call, management said that it plans to triple its salesforce headcount due to its recent success&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;And among other improvements, the Apollo platform has helped the company greatly reduce the costs and time required to get a customer up and running&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Being able to better target customers and onboard them quickly while providing a best-in-class and sticky data platform points to a bright future for Palantir&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Bear Case&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Double-Edged Business Model&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;While Palantir’s differentiated services and business model is one of the company’s key strengths, there are also several downsides as well&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;First, due to the custom-built solutions Palantir offers, the company undergoes a costly and complicated minimum 6 month sales cycle that can often amount to nothing&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Second, even if a customer jumps on board, contracts are cancelable with a typical notice of 3-6 months&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Third, the deep history it has with customers results in a very top-heavy concentration &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;As of the third quarter of 2020, the top 20 customers represented 61% of the company’s revenue, which notably is down from 73% from the year prior&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Lastly, the deal-by-deal nature of Palantir’s business model means that the sources of revenue are lumpy and hard to predict, which can be a cause of concern for investors&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Biden Administration and Negative Headline Risk&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;First, Peter Thiel was an outspoken supporter of Trump, who increased defense spending 5% a year while Obama decreased spending 3% a year. &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;While I don’t think this will be a long-term issue, a Biden presidency does represent a potential decrease in defense budgets which could hinder Palantir’s growth with Gotham&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;However, it is important to note that management during its latest earnings call did address this issue, stating that it has worked with many administrations across the world and doesn’t foresee this to be a problem&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Second, Palantir has been targeted by the media several times for giving the government too much power and the political and social environment in which the tide seems to be turning against tech could present Palantir with headaches in the future &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;This risk is also further exacerbated by the fact that Palantir is 49.9999% owned by its co-founders, who are outspoken and strongly opinionated. Clear corporate governance risk.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tough Competition in Commercial Space&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;In my opinion the largest obstacle Palantir faces is its ability to execute in the commercial space&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Palantir offers an expensive, premium, custom-built end-to-end solution for clients, which is great for the government but not exactly what most businesses are looking for&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Instead, most large scale businesses have already invested heavily into their own systems and want to buy best-in-class piecemeal solutions from different tech companies&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Several notable businesses left Palantir from 2019 to 2020, including JP Morgan, Coca Cola, and American Express, and this decreased the customer count from 133 to 125&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;However, one important thing to note is that in the latest earnings call, Palantir’s management openly addressed this issue and the company has already started to provide solutions that are modular, which means customers can take the individual solutions they want rather than adopting the entire Foundry system &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;This also allows the company to offer different price points which may allow Palantir to be more competitive in the market&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Recent news of bringing on BP and IBM as clients could also be a sign that its Foundry business may be ready for mass adoption&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lock-up Expiration&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Because this is a short-term risk, I’m adding this as a bonus bearish reason&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Palantir went public through a direct listing on September 30, 2020, during which up to 20% of shares were available to trade&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;The remaining 80% is available to trade starting February 19th when the lockup expires and this could lead to a flooding of shares being sold and at the very least, volatility caused by the uncertainty&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Financials and Valuation&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Starting off with the income statement,&lt;/strong&gt; the important things to note is that from 2018 to 2019, the company has grown revenue by about 25% while maintaining roughly the same amount in operating expenses, which speaks to the improved operational efficiency of the company &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;The company has guided to $1.07 billion for the full year of 2020, which represents a 44% year over year increase and for a company with 1 billion in revenue, increasing revenue growth is a great sign&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Comparing Q3 2020 to Q3 2019, the company was able to increase average revenue per customer by 38% and grew commercial revenue by 35% and government revenue by 68%&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;With all this said, one piece of concern in Palantir’s income statement is its net losses. The company has not been able to turn a profit in its entire history, but it did report positive adjusted operating income in its latest quarter when adjusted for stock based compensation&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Moving onto its latest cash flow statement,&lt;/strong&gt; what you mainly need to know is that the company has recently had a huge stock based compensation expense this past year due to the direct listing, so if you were to add that back, the company is essentially near break-even &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;However, the company’s free cash flow (operating cash flow minus your capital expenditures) is negative, so the company still is clearly losing money although much less than even a year prior&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Lastly, Palantir has a great balance sheet&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;With $1.8 billion in cash and only $200mm in debt, the company is in a great position to fuel its future growth&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Regarding the company’s valuation,&lt;/strong&gt; while the company is growing nicely at 44% from 2019-2020, and is expected to grow 31% from 2020-2021 based on street estimates, it currently trades around a 45x NTM sales multiple depending on the day, which makes it one of the most expensive companies on the market &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;The key question here is do you want to pay an extremely high premium for a company that does have a best-in-class software or wait for a better entry point?&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What I’m Doing&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Personally, I can&amp;#39;t justify Palantir&amp;#39;s valuation, which may sound a little old-school but I think there are better opportunities out there&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;However, in the long-run I am bullish on the company and would buy on any major dips in the 20s (and teens if it somehow falls down to that)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;I&amp;#39;m also closely monitoring what happens after earnings (2/16) and next week the lock-up expires on 2/19 so it&amp;#39;ll be interesting to see what happens to the stock then&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TLDR:&lt;/strong&gt; Palantir has a best-in-class, sticky data platform that it offers to both the government side (where it&amp;#39;s pretty much a monopoly) and businesses (which is picking up steam with tweaks to the business model and a growing salesforce). Growing healthy top-line but unprofitable and trading at a higher valuation than almost all other software companies. I am holding off on buying for now but would welcome major dips as great buying opportunities.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/user/rareliquid&quot;&gt; /u/rareliquid &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/lih6ee/full_diligence_post_on_palantir_pltr_earnings/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/lih6ee/full_diligence_post_on_palantir_pltr_earnings/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t3_lih6ee</id><link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/lih6ee/full_diligence_post_on_palantir_pltr_earnings/" /><updated>2021-02-12T18:23:04+00:00</updated><title>Full Diligence Post on Palantir (PLTR) - Earnings Next Monday (2/16) &amp; Lockup Expiration (2/19)</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/RoPrime12</name><uri>https://www.reddit.com/user/RoPrime12</uri></author><category term="investing" label="r/investing"/><content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;In 2010 legendary investor and founder of the Baupost Group Seth Klarman described in his annual letter 20 lessons from the financial crisis which were either never learned or else immediately forgotten by most market participants. With him at the helm the Baupost Group has averaged around 18% and that since 1982 - a spectacular return. Some of these lessons are even more relevant today. I took the most important ones and updated it for the current market.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;Things that have never happened before are bound to occur with some regularity. You must always be prepared for the unexpected, including sudden, sharp downward swings in markets and the economy. Whatever adverse scenario you can contemplate, reality can be far worse.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;Nassim Taleb calls these “Black Swans”: an event that comes as a surprise, has a major effect, and is often inappropriately rationalized after the fact with the benefit of&lt;a href=&quot;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Hindsight&quot;&gt; &lt;/a&gt;hindsight. Examples would be the Internet, the personal Computer, World War I, the dissolution of the Soviet Union, 9/11 and of course the Coronavirus.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;These all changed countries or continents for decades. With shutdown still in place in several countries in the world the economy’s output is much lower than it was at the end of 2019 - yet we reached an all time high in the stock market. New Mutations are evolving and there might be a sharp downturn in the future or there might not. History taught us that market crashes are much more common than we think. So it is important to be diversified in different asset classes, industries and countries to be protected against those changes.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;When excesses such as lax lending standards become widespread and persist for some time, people are lulled into a false sense of security, creating an even more dangerous situation. In some cases, excesses migrate beyond regional or national borders, raising the ante for investors and governments. These excesses will eventually end, triggering a crisis at least in proportion to the degree of the excesses. Correlations between asset classes may be surprisingly high when leverage rapidly unwinds.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;With interest rates in Europe being partly negative and extremely low in the US, people are lulled into borrowing to get onto the Party of rising stocks, and that on margin. Margin on Portfolio reached an all time high in December of 2020 and the number of retail traders thanks to Robin Hood exploded even with the recent controversy. In addition - central banks in Europe and the US are printing money like there is no tomorrow. These money policies have driven stocks to a new high. And the excess of government debt mirrored that progression. Action always have consequences - but however harsh they may be one thing is certain: If the current price is higher, the returns won’t be as great in the future.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;Nowhere does it say that investors should strive to make every last dollar of potential profit; consideration of risk must never take a backseat to return. Conservative positioning entering a crisis is crucial: it enables one to maintain long-term oriented, clear thinking, and to focus on new opportunities while others are distracted or even forced to sell. Portfolio hedges must be in place before a crisis hits. One cannot reliably or affordably increase or replace hedges that are rolling off during a financial crisis.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;We all chase profits, that is just how it is. However conservative positioning and a long-term oriented perspective is crucial. Most people in 2000 thought they would buy the dip when their favourite stocks started to decline, however the decline didn’t stop. The Nasdaq posted a loss of 77%, which would take 15 years to regain the dotcom bubble. During the financial crisis many couldn’t sell their stock because there were no buyers - even retail investors that thought they could get out couldn’t.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;During it Janus Funds were similar to ARK today. Investing in modern technology companies and industry they were one of the top cutting edge technologies. Janus were lauded as great money managers but the end of the bubble resulted in brutal loses. Cathie Wood is one of the smartest investors today, but one has to keep in mind the inherent risk that comes with her investment strategy.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Similarly we saw extreme loses in GME. Chasing after returns purely on performance will not result in great results.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;Risk is not inherent in an investment; it is always relative to the price paid. Uncertainty is not the same as risk. Indeed, when great uncertainty – such as in the fall of 2008 – drives securities prices to especially low levels, they often become less risky investments.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;This is the quintessential art of investing. Your returns will entirely depend on what price you paid. Microsoft was a great company, but buying it during the dotcom bubble would leave you 15 years with no returns and several other well known companies like Cisco or Intel never reached their dot-com peak. Your returns are entirely dependent on the price you pay and so is the risk factor.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;Do not trust financial market risk models. Reality is always too complex to be accurately modeled. Attention to risk must be a 24/7/365 obsession, with people – not computers – assessing and reassessing the risk environment in real time. Despite the predilection of some analysts to model the financial markets using sophisticated mathematics, the markets are governed by behavioral science, not physical science.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;Because of this behavior we see certain securities being extremely highly valued like Zoom at the moment and certain sectors being very depressed like oil until recently. Yet oil is seen as extremely risky, even though the projected use of oil will increase in the next 10 years. That means that you can find bargains all the time. Those bargains are declared risky - while the overvalued stocks are declared safe. Microsoft after the dotcom bubble only recovered in 2016. 15 years of no gains at all - yet now Microsoft is treated like a company that will be a great stock forever. It is a great company, but the same was thought about companies like Polaroid or Kodak - we saw how it turned out.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;Do not accept principal risk while investing short-term cash: the greedy effort to earn a few extra basis points of yield inevitably leads to the incurrence of greater risk, which increases the likelihood of losses and severe illiquidity at precisely the moment when cash is needed to cover expenses, to meet commitments, or to make compelling long-term investments.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;This can be highly dangerous and I see it all the time here on reddit. Someone wants to use the money in 3-5 years to buy a house, yet instead of proposing a portfolio that is safe and diversified in several asset classes, most propose a stock only portfolio and sometimes even sector or ARK ETFs. Research has shown that a stock only portfolio will beat pretty much every other asset allocation - that is over the long term. Due to the ups and downs of the market it doesn’t guarantee returns in 3-5 years or even worse can lead to loses. From 1929-1954,1973-1982 and from 2000-2013 the S&amp;amp;P 500 has shown long stretches of no absolute return. Investing before a correction that you cannot foresee would result in either big loses or in the inability to purchase that house - often both. So be conservative when you need the money.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;The latest trade of a security creates a dangerous illusion that its market price approximates its true value. This mirage is especially dangerous during periods of market exuberance. The concept of &amp;quot;private market value&amp;quot; as an anchor to the proper valuation of a business can also be greatly skewed during ebullient times and should always be considered with a healthy degree of skepticism.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;This is especially true today. Many stocks are currently at outrageous prices. I don’t talk about the FANGMAN stocks - these have great growth and while still being historically overvalued not outrageously so. Several EV/Green/Biotech/Weed/Technology stocks are seen as the next big Google without decent cash flows and while competing in the same space.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;This is especially true for unprofitable companies at the moment. According to Joel Greenblatt: If you bought every company that lost money in 2019 that had a market cap over $1 billion, and so they’re about 261 companies, you’ll be up 85 percent so far until today. Something like that won’t be sustainable.Looking at the fundamentals behind the business often makes it clear how unreasonable some of these numbers are - and what returns should be expected of them (often negative)&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;You must buy on the way down. There is far more volume on the way down than on the way back up, and far less competition among buyers. It is almost always better to be too early than too late, but you must be prepared for price markdowns on what you buy.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;We saw that during the financial crisis and also again in 2020. Those that bought on the way down were generously rewarded. You never know when the bottom will hit especially since everyone will run around in panic like a beheaded henn. Researching the fundamentals of a company one can score great businesses for cheap. However they might go down a bit in the short term due to market panic.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;Financial innovation can be highly dangerous, though almost no one will tell you this. New financial products are typically created for sunny days and are almost never stress-tested for stormy weather. Securitization is an area that almost perfectly fits this description; markets for securitized assets such as subprime mortgages completely collapsed in 2008 and have not fully recovered. Ironically, the government is eager to restore the securitization markets back to their pre-collapse stature.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;As SPACs and Bitcoin dominate the current market this warning is very important. SPACs and the companies behind them haven’t had the greatest return over the long term. With the explosion of SPACs going public, chances are high that those financial products can be very dangerous. Add the risk that SPAC managers often get big compensation packages and try to hide information to increase the price (DOJ Investigation from Clover), these investments should be taken with the utmost caution. Not only that but they also compete in the same space.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The same applies to bitcoin. While I believe that cryptocurrencies will have a bright future, they have yet to be tested during prolonged market downturn where the market was negative not just a few week but several months or even years. No one know what the price will be then and some investors might wake up to a bad surprise. It is important to know these risks.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;Ratings agencies are highly conflicted, unimaginative dupes. They are blissfully unaware of adverse selection and moral hazard. Investors should never trust them.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;That what makes short seller research so important. While there are a lot of crocks in the financial market (both on the long and the short side), these people often find what the rating agencies or investment banks ignore. If you invest into a company and there is a short report don’t dismiss it - often they include information that was previously overlooked.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;Be sure that you are well compensated for illiquidity – especially illiquidity without control – because it can create particularly high opportunity costs.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;The OTC market absolutely exploded in 2020. Many of these are highly illiquid. Be prepared for the risk.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;Beware leverage in all its forms. Borrowers – individual, corporate, or government – should always match fund their liabilities against the duration of their assets. Borrowers must always remember that capital markets can be extremely fickle, and that it is never safe to assume a maturing loan can be rolled over. Even if you are unleveraged, the leverage employed by others can drive dramatic price and valuation swings; sudden unavailability of leverage in the economy may trigger an economic downturn.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;Everyone takes debt at the moment. It is so cheap that many companies use debt to do buybacks or otherwise increase their price. Other people trade on margin and governments don&amp;#39;t seem to care about debt. That can be highly dangerous. No one can control interests rates over the long run and bankruptcy is the most surefire way to delete any investment returns. Peter Lynch said: “If you have no debt it is very hard to go bankrupt”. While businesses with little or no debt might not rise to the same degree, they will reduce the chance of a wipeout significantly.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;When a government official says a problem has been &amp;quot;contained,&amp;quot; pay no attention.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;The government – the ultimate short-term-oriented player – cannot withstand much pain in the economy or the financial markets. Bailouts and rescues are likely to occur, though not with sufficient predictability for investors to comfortably take advantage. The government will take enormous risks in such interventions, especially if the expenses can be conveniently deferred to the future. Some of the price-tag is in the form of back- stops and guarantees, whose cost is almost impossible to determine.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/blockquote&gt; &lt;p&gt;We saw that in March the Fed stepped in and bailed out the market. A decrease in interest rates and intense money printing. However the question is: How long can it continue and what will happen to those expenses in the future? All action has consequences and we saw that some of them can end quite bad.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Seth Klarman also added some false lessons, that are relevant without commentary.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;False Lessons&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ol&gt; &lt;li&gt;There are no long-term lessons – ever.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Bad things happen, but really bad things do not. Do buy the dips, especially the lowest quality securities when they come under pressure, because declines will quickly be&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;There is no amount of bad news that the markets cannot see past.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;If you’ve just stared into the abyss, quickly forget it: the lessons of history can only hold you back.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Excess capacity in people, machines, or property will be quickly absorbed.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Markets need not be in sync with one another. Simultaneously, the bond market can be priced for sustained tough times, the equity market for a strong recovery, and gold for high inflation. Such an apparent disconnect is indefinitely sustainable.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;In a crisis, stocks of financial companies are great investments, because the tide is bound to turn. Massive losses on bad loans and soured investments are irrelevant to value; improving trends and future prospects are what matter, regardless of whether profits will have to be used to cover loan losses and equity shortfalls for years to come.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;The government can reasonably rely on debt ratings when it forms programs to lend money to buyers of otherwise unattractive debt instruments.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;The government can indefinitely control both short-term and long-term interest rates.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;The government can always rescue the markets or interfere with contract law whenever it deems convenient with little or no apparent cost. (Investors believe this now and, worse still, the government believes it as well. We are probably doomed to a lasting legacy of government tampering with financial markets and the economy, which is likely to create the mother of all moral hazards. The government is blissfully unaware of the wisdom of Friedrich Hayek: “The curious task of economics is to demonstrate to men how little they really know about what they imagine they can design.”)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ol&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Hope you enjoyed my little writeup. Feel free to post any questions!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/user/RoPrime12&quot;&gt; /u/RoPrime12 &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/li6vyf/forgotten_lessons_of_2008_that_are_even_more/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/li6vyf/forgotten_lessons_of_2008_that_are_even_more/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t3_li6vyf</id><link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/li6vyf/forgotten_lessons_of_2008_that_are_even_more/" /><updated>2021-02-12T08:23:45+00:00</updated><title>Forgotten lessons of 2008 that are even more relevant today</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/_amc_</name><uri>https://www.reddit.com/user/_amc_</uri></author><category term="investing" label="r/investing"/><content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Found this 2018 article, interesting/fun fact: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.nytimes.com/2018/02/02/your-money/stock-market-after-hours-trading.html&quot;&gt;The Stock Market Works by Day, but It Loves the Night&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;If you had bought the SPY at the last second of trading on each business day since 1993 and sold at the market open the next day — capturing all of the net after-hour gains — your cumulative price gain would be 571%&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;On the other hand, if you had done the reverse, buying the ETF at the first second of regular trading every morning at 9:30 a.m. and selling at the 4 p.m. close, you would be down 4.4%&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;Chart: &lt;a href=&quot;https://i.imgur.com/YPTjg3v.jpg&quot;&gt;https://i.imgur.com/YPTjg3v.jpg&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Disclaimer - I&amp;#39;m not posting this to endorse the above strategy, I prefer to buy and hold.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/user/_amc_&quot;&gt; /u/_amc_ &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/lhtodm/historically_its_way_better_to_invest_at_market/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/lhtodm/historically_its_way_better_to_invest_at_market/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t3_lhtodm</id><link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/lhtodm/historically_its_way_better_to_invest_at_market/" /><updated>2021-02-11T20:19:14+00:00</updated><title>Historically it's way better to invest at market close than at market open, most gains occur overnight</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/goldschmiede</name><uri>https://www.reddit.com/user/goldschmiede</uri></author><category term="investing" label="r/investing"/><content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;As of posting, ABX is Currently just above $28 CAD&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Barrick Gold has a solid record of profitable income. It has an almost unheard of sub 13 P/E ratio in this inflationary market (DOW average is 31.5). The company pays a small dividend. Just opened another mine, which is set to add to their production. Fuel is cheap, workers are spread out and covid exposure in this business is low.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Warren Buffett took a large position last year, later reducing his position. Gold down in the past months (still slowly falling) - yet inflation is at record highs.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Seems like a buy and hold in this market. This is not financial advice and all that. Do your own research.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/user/goldschmiede&quot;&gt; /u/goldschmiede &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/liej8k/abx_barrick_gold_trending_downwards_but/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/liej8k/abx_barrick_gold_trending_downwards_but/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t3_liej8k</id><link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/liej8k/abx_barrick_gold_trending_downwards_but/" /><updated>2021-02-12T16:26:56+00:00</updated><title>$ABX - Barrick Gold - trending downwards, but tremendous value.</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/Okmanl</name><uri>https://www.reddit.com/user/Okmanl</uri></author><category term="investing" label="r/investing"/><content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;quot;Analysts have been calling the stock “overvalued” since the day they went public, because they all keep comparing it to other car companies. I wish I had a dollar for every analyst who pointed out how “&lt;em&gt;every other car company sells ten times as many cars&lt;/em&gt;”. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I’ve also repeatedly bumped into some lazy analysis that Tesla is expensive because its current P/E is 1,270x or forward P/E is 204x. However, I’ve hardly ever seen a Tesla bear put out a detailed valuation in support of their bearish thesis which makes me wonder if a lot of people are simply dismissing Tesla in arrogance.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;But the thing is, they’re all making the same mistake:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Tesla isn’t a car company.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;They’re an energy and technology and SaaS company that makes cars.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Once you realize what Tesla really is, you start to see what their place in the market is going to be in the years to come.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;They acquired Grohmann Engineering. They acquired Perbox. They acquired Maxwell Technologies and Hibar Systems. And of course everyone remembers the Solar City acquisition back before dropping Motors from their name. They didn’t acquire these companies because they thought they were cool. They did it so nobody else could.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;There are 25,000 EV charging stations in the United States. 20,000 of them are owned by Tesla.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Tesla is currently the #1 li-ion battery manufacturer in America, and #5 in the world.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Tesla has secured the rights to large supplies of lithium, and has developed their own internal process for extracting lithium deposits inexpensively from other sources.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;These segments of the energy space — battery production and EV charging — are a market sector that’s going to grow 50 fold in the next 15 years as consumer demand for EV’s increases. All of the major auto manufacturers have declared they’re shifting towards electric cars.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Where are they going to get the batteries? How are their customers going to charge them?&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The answer: Tesla.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Musk has made it clear from the beginning that their intent is to supply batteries for the entire EV &lt;em&gt;industry&lt;/em&gt;, not just their own cars, and has also more or less come out and said that he’s open to letting other auto manufacturers access their Supercharger network. That puts them squarely in the energy business as the single most capable distributor.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;There’s also been chatter about licensing their self-driving technology, and using their self-driving technology as a recurring revenue generation, which would be a very attractive value-add for the other OEM’s. And all of these things don’t even begin to cover the expected growth in residential energy with products like rooftop solar, Powerwall, etc.&amp;quot;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;People making the claim that Tesla is an overvalued car company are making the same mistake they made saying Amazon is an overvalued retail company, after it was clear how big AWS and cloud computing was going to become.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/user/Okmanl&quot;&gt; /u/Okmanl &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/ling8b/why_cathie_wood_might_be_right_and_why_tsla_is/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/ling8b/why_cathie_wood_might_be_right_and_why_tsla_is/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t3_ling8b</id><link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/ling8b/why_cathie_wood_might_be_right_and_why_tsla_is/" /><updated>2021-02-12T23:14:42+00:00</updated><title>Why Cathie Wood might be right, and why TSLA is actually STILL fairly or even undervalued at these levels.</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/Canuhere</name><uri>https://www.reddit.com/user/Canuhere</uri></author><category term="investing" label="r/investing"/><content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hi Everyone, this is my first semi-dd post on here. I got into $ITRM for about $500 a few days back without really knowing anything about it, a foolish move by a green investor. Only foolish because I bought it without knowing anything about the stock and just saw some conversation about it on stocktwits.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Well, since then it has gone down, so I decided to learn about what it actually is and if I should be patient or cut my losses. I have learned some about FDA approval processes, offerings, urinary tract infections, and that drug companies can exist for some time hemorrhaging money without ever having released a drug before! I found this all to be very interesting! I&amp;#39;d like to share the basics of what I learned, and also get opinions on this stock....&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The company as mentioned, is a &amp;quot;clinical-stage pharmaceutical company&amp;quot;, which I take to basically mean they have no approved drugs yet. My friend called it a gofundme for drugs when I explained it to him lol. They have been working on one drug, oral antibiotics for treating UTIs, which currently does not exist.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;They have complete phase 3 (of which there are 4 phases) trials with good results and have applied with the FDA for approval(NDA). Approval for this drug is on FDAs &amp;quot;priority list&amp;quot;, meaning if approved it is somewhat fast-tracked through the approval process. Expected approval is July of this year.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;From my research I gather that the majority of drugs that pass phase 3 and apply for NDA are eventually approved. Something like over 80%. The company has also recently made a public offering of almost 2 million shares to raise capital that will cover operating expenses until 2023 (that happened a few days ago). They also recently created an agreement with a firm that specializes in assisting drug companies in the final phases of development to bring the drug to market(also very recent activity).&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The stock price has really only gone down since the IPO and is currently at almost an all time low.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;To me, it seems like the approval of this drug is imminent. Why would they be partnering with a company to hash out the logistics of the release if this weren&amp;#39;t the case? Why would they still be raising capital if this were not the case? I have a strong sense that the drug will be approved.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Are there any experienced pharma investors here that can chime in on this or give their thoughts?&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Does it follow that if the drug is approved the price will go up as I predict? Or is the price built in?&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I think there is still quite some dd to do on this such as what would the drug cost and how many people need it, what is the competition, etc. Starting to look into these things but it gets pretty complicated.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Still a lot to learn but I feel good about this investment after my initial blindfolded dart throw.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Thanks for reading.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/user/Canuhere&quot;&gt; /u/Canuhere &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/lihv5p/itrm_and_pharma_investing/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/lihv5p/itrm_and_pharma_investing/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t3_lihv5p</id><link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/lihv5p/itrm_and_pharma_investing/" /><updated>2021-02-12T18:53:36+00:00</updated><title>$ITRM and pharma investing</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/SeanVo</name><uri>https://www.reddit.com/user/SeanVo</uri></author><category term="investing" label="r/investing"/><content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The market has brought so much growth to many portfolios over the last 10+ years, it&amp;#39;s been a wonderful ride. I&amp;#39;ve developed decent skills identifying sectors that are in favor, buying and holding low cost index funds and sector ETF&amp;#39;s focused on technology and innovation.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Long-term charts of market performance show there are periods of decline. Sometimes weeks to months (Covid in February - March of 2020) and sometimes a number of years (August 2000 - March 2003). My portfolio was reduced quite a bit between 2000 and 2003. I held on, rode it down, and back up.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Just like earthquakes, fires, and floods, it&amp;#39;s good to think through a plan before the event comes. What&amp;#39;s your plan to make it through a bear market?&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Some presumably wise investors like having some cash on the side to pickup bargains during downturns. Some did that during the Covid drop. There are others that would either short the overall market on the way down, or buy inverse ETF&amp;#39;s (ProShares for example. &lt;em&gt;Side note&lt;/em&gt;: holding leveraged inverse funds for a long period of time, even a few days, can lead to unpredictable results due to decay.) If you have a longer time horizon until retirement, riding it down and back up would likely be better than selling at some point and missing the rebound.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;What&amp;#39;s your plan?&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/user/SeanVo&quot;&gt; /u/SeanVo &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/liilvv/preparing_to_fight_a_bear_market_someday/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/liilvv/preparing_to_fight_a_bear_market_someday/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t3_liilvv</id><link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/liilvv/preparing_to_fight_a_bear_market_someday/" /><updated>2021-02-12T19:25:57+00:00</updated><title>Preparing to fight a bear (market) someday</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/Tropink</name><uri>https://www.reddit.com/user/Tropink</uri></author><category term="investing" label="r/investing"/><content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Big Bank, won’t bust. Stock is down from $48 before pandemic to $33, hasn’t gone back up while others banks have, trading below book value. Fake accounts CEO and people involved in it are long gone, banned from banking altogether even, stock undervalued by investors who don’t trust the bank even though it’s management has been completely revamped, but consumers forget faster, new CEO has a lot of experience, knows how a good bank works, worked with Visa and Chase. Priced in massive inefficiency which is decreasing thanks to the new CEO’s efforts and can only decrease. Regulators have been steadily removing restrictions, asset cap being the big one to watch out for, it has cost WFC around 4 billion dollars, the stock is gonna go up a lot once it does. You’re probablynot gonna get rich off of WFC but it’s as sure of a bet as you can get, while also not making peanuts, it has a lot of room to not only recover from pre-pandemic price, but to increase even more.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/user/Tropink&quot;&gt; /u/Tropink &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/ligccs/wfc_wells_fargo_dd_why_i_am_bullish_on_wells_fargo/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/ligccs/wfc_wells_fargo_dd_why_i_am_bullish_on_wells_fargo/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t3_ligccs</id><link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/ligccs/wfc_wells_fargo_dd_why_i_am_bullish_on_wells_fargo/" /><updated>2021-02-12T17:46:53+00:00</updated><title>$WFC - Wells Fargo DD; Why I am bullish on Wells Fargo</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/reddituser9439</name><uri>https://www.reddit.com/user/reddituser9439</uri></author><category term="investing" label="r/investing"/><content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Let&amp;#39;s talk about futures contracts for &lt;em&gt;imperishable goods&lt;/em&gt;, lets just use &amp;quot;widgets&amp;quot; as an example, and let&amp;#39;s assume there is &lt;em&gt;no margin or loan or leverage or fractional escrow involved.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Here is my (maybe wrong) understanding of how a futures contract works:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;When you purchase a futures contract you agree to buy or sell widgets at a certain price at a later date. Without any margin (borrowing) involved, the company that set up the contract (the broker) holds/locks the full amount of both the widgets and USD in escrow until the agreed-upon date, and then just swaps the two accounts on that date. Basically they hold the money in one hand, and widgets in another hand, then swap hands at the end of the contract.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What I don&amp;#39;t understand at all:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The futures contracts sell at almost the exact same price as the current value of widgets. Why not just purchase widgets? If I buy a contract today for 1 widget at $1 on June 30, and on June 30 the price is $2, I made $1. But if I outright bought 1 widget today at $1 and sell on June 30 for $2 I would make the same amount. Why would I want to tie up my money in an escrow account for months and risk the escrow company going under during that time if I could just buy the underlying asset? I&amp;#39;m so confused. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Maybe the price of the futures doesn&amp;#39;t always exactly track the current price of the underlying asset?&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;When/why would this happen? Is it a sign of anything?&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/user/reddituser9439&quot;&gt; /u/reddituser9439 &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/liizuh/i_dont_understand_the_point_of_futures_markets/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/liizuh/i_dont_understand_the_point_of_futures_markets/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t3_liizuh</id><link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/liizuh/i_dont_understand_the_point_of_futures_markets/" /><updated>2021-02-12T19:43:55+00:00</updated><title>I don't understand the point of futures markets for imperishable goods. Please enlighten me.</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/thri54</name><uri>https://www.reddit.com/user/thri54</uri></author><category term="investing" label="r/investing"/><content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;That title is worse than it sounds. We need to talk about shipping:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;For anyone who hasn&amp;#39;t looked at a maritime shipping/bulker/tanker company: A) Good choice! B) The value of these companies is almost all assets. This is one of the few places you&amp;#39;ll still see companies trade at/below book value. Star Bulker Carriers, for example, has $2.9 billion in ships, $1.5 billion in net equity, and a $1.2 Billion market cap. Frontline has $1.5 Billion in equity, $1.3 billion market cap. That doesn&amp;#39;t mean you should go out and buy $SBLK or $FRO. The business is an asset heavy, miserably unprofitable commodity service. Everyone in the shipping industry waits around cutting their teeth until a shipping supercycle hits and they can actually profit. They have extreme sensitivity to interest rates, and extreme sensitivity to economic downturns.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;You aren&amp;#39;t getting $1 for $.90 buying these stocks. You&amp;#39;re getting the expected future cashflows from $1 of net merchant ship, which the market ascribes an NPV of &amp;lt;$1.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I digress. Castor, as of 9/30, has $30 million in ships. Six 75,000 DWT bulkers, to be exact. A tiny fleet. They&amp;#39;ve now bought a Capesize and 2 LR2 tankers. Lets call that an extra $80 million. $110MM in ships. Their market cap, as of close, is $880MM. 8x price/assets for merchant ships! WHAT? It&amp;#39;s not uncommon for this company&amp;#39;s peers to trade at .3x price/assets!&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;That&amp;#39;s... a bad investment. Quite possibly the worst investment opportunity I&amp;#39;ve ever seen. At least most bubbles have some &amp;quot;moonshot&amp;quot; potential; these guys buy boats. Sell. Run. This is the dumbest bubble I&amp;#39;ve ever seen.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;TLDR: This is the top, lads.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/user/thri54&quot;&gt; /u/thri54 &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/li4uaz/castor_maritime_ctrm_to_buy_two_lr2_tankers_for/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/li4uaz/castor_maritime_ctrm_to_buy_two_lr2_tankers_for/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t3_li4uaz</id><link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/li4uaz/castor_maritime_ctrm_to_buy_two_lr2_tankers_for/" /><updated>2021-02-12T05:48:25+00:00</updated><title>Castor Maritime ($CTRM) to buy two LR2 tankers for $27MM. Market Cap jumps $250MM.</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/BlueHotChiliPeppers</name><uri>https://www.reddit.com/user/BlueHotChiliPeppers</uri></author><category term="investing" label="r/investing"/><content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;I am quite new to investment and have the last year invested 90% of my money into a tech fund and have I got like 20% profit, like everything else in the marked. However, I am constantly in fear that we are living in a bubble are now researching timing to when to sell. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Due to hype is lots of subreddits full of bloat and optimism (even though many users on &lt;a href=&quot;/r/investing&quot;&gt;r/investing&lt;/a&gt; is keeping calm). Do anyone have tips for what other discussion forums I should check out, such as subreddits, good youtube channels etc, to find a reasonable analysis of the situation?&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/user/BlueHotChiliPeppers&quot;&gt; /u/BlueHotChiliPeppers &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/liauyb/good_sources_for_bubble_discussions/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/liauyb/good_sources_for_bubble_discussions/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t3_liauyb</id><link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/liauyb/good_sources_for_bubble_discussions/" /><updated>2021-02-12T13:18:48+00:00</updated><title>Good sources for bubble discussions</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/zen_boss</name><uri>https://www.reddit.com/user/zen_boss</uri></author><category term="investing" label="r/investing"/><content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hey everyone &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m new at investing and trying to do my DD before investing. What do you all think about TIXT? &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;They just partnered with google to transform digital customer experience management (DCXM). That market is supposed to grow by 20-25% annually. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I work in this field, using AI for better customer management and i think it has a lot of potential. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;TIXT, a subsidiary of TU is trading sideways at around $30 now. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;What else should I be looking at? Any thoughts?&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2021/02/09/2171892/0/en/TELUS-and-Google-Form-Strategic-Alliance-to-Bring-Digital-Transformation-to-Key-Industries-Including-Communications-Technology-Healthcare-and-Agriculture.html&quot;&gt;https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2021/02/09/2171892/0/en/TELUS-and-Google-Form-Strategic-Alliance-to-Bring-Digital-Transformation-to-Key-Industries-Including-Communications-Technology-Healthcare-and-Agriculture.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/user/zen_boss&quot;&gt; /u/zen_boss &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/lijn15/tixt_telus_international_tech_investment/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/lijn15/tixt_telus_international_tech_investment/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t3_lijn15</id><link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/lijn15/tixt_telus_international_tech_investment/" /><updated>2021-02-12T20:13:29+00:00</updated><title>TIXT TELUS INTERNATIONAL | Tech investment</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/Hichek2</name><uri>https://www.reddit.com/user/Hichek2</uri></author><category term="investing" label="r/investing"/><content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;For the past two-quarters, people have been wondering whether Berkshire Hathaway or not. In Q3 Berkshire Hathaway added a new position that was not disclosed in 13F, people were wondering that was legal or not? and it is legal, Berkshire Hathaway secured permission from the regulators to not disclose its most recent purchase. That permission only last one reporting period, which was Q3. Today, we&amp;#39;ll find out what that purchase was, and I&amp;#39;m thinking it was TESLA. Is only a matter of hours before we find out. If it is revealed that Berkshire Hathaway bought TESLA, that is a gave changer.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;So far Vanguard and Blackrock have increased their position in TESLA, with Warren on board we could see $1,000 by the beginning of April.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I will keep an eye on the SEC website this afternoon and let you guys know whether he bought it or not.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Disclaimer: I am not a financial advisor, always do your own due diligence, and YES I bought the tesla DIP today.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Bridgewater Q4 13F just became public -most notable new acquisition &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://whalewisdom.com/stock/pdd-2&quot;&gt;&lt;strong&gt;PDD&lt;/strong&gt; Pinduoduo Inc&lt;/a&gt;&lt;strong&gt;1.21%&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Still waiting for Berkshire Hathaway - is released AH. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&amp;#x200B;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/user/Hichek2&quot;&gt; /u/Hichek2 &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/lieh0u/today_is_the_day_today_we_will_find_out_if_warren/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/lieh0u/today_is_the_day_today_we_will_find_out_if_warren/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t3_lieh0u</id><link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/lieh0u/today_is_the_day_today_we_will_find_out_if_warren/" /><updated>2021-02-12T16:24:05+00:00</updated><title>TODAY is the DAY! Today we will find out if Warren Bought Tesla during Q3 &amp; Q4</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/JamesHolden1975</name><uri>https://www.reddit.com/user/JamesHolden1975</uri></author><category term="investing" label="r/investing"/><content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Amtech Systems ASYS provides capital equipment to the semiconductor industry especially those that supply chips for autos. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Yesterday some of the headlines&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.google.com/amp/s/www.theverge.com/platform/amp/2021/2/11/22278431/biden-administration-global-semiconductor-chip-shortage-executive-order&quot;&gt;Global Semiconductor Shortage&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;ASYS started lest year quite nicely with rapidly rising revenues and then coronavirus hit and all the semiconductor companies stopped their expansion and went into capital preservation. This hurt ASYS and took what started as a good year and made it OK. For a small company they have little debt and 45 million in cash. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;This year is still Covid effected as many orders are in the urgent discussion phase. So revenues this quarter came in at 18 million at the high end of guidance but lower that a pre Covid first quarter last year.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Going forward ASYS projects Q2 2021 to be at 18-20 million vs 14.5 million last year. The discussions with big names since they provide equipment to 3 out of the top 5 power semiconductors is getting urgent. You should listen to their conference call to hear more. &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;A larger alternative to smaller ASYS would be Applied Materials AMAT which will see huge growth due to all the capital expansion. This is pretty heavy with the supply shortage being such big news. Everything is getting smarter and needing semiconductors now a days.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/user/JamesHolden1975&quot;&gt; /u/JamesHolden1975 &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/liaaaq/asys_for_the_semiconductor_shortage/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/liaaaq/asys_for_the_semiconductor_shortage/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t3_liaaaq</id><link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/liaaaq/asys_for_the_semiconductor_shortage/" /><updated>2021-02-12T12:42:54+00:00</updated><title>ASYS for the semiconductor shortage.</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/eni1993</name><uri>https://www.reddit.com/user/eni1993</uri></author><category term="investing" label="r/investing"/><content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;TODAY I HAD TIME TO MAKE THE POST FROM PC So a better format on this one.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;ETHT&lt;/strong&gt;: Price target: 135 max - 47 min - atm 58.8 EPS growth: Positive. Q420: Expected positive wich they will announce on 18th i think. *Today we had some falldown on this but i added few more stocks after the today sell of Well Stocks that get at 29.10% in just 2 days with x5 leverage.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Bought 300 stocks at 50.29 Leverage x1 Atm +8.99%&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Bought 50 stocks at 50.38 Leverage x5 Atm +43.47%&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;12/2 Bought 60 stocks at 56.13 Leverage x1 (x5 Leverage closed because of 18 Feb and propably alot of open x5 leverage trades on this one) Atm -2.5%&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Take Profit at Price Target 62 or 19 Feb. Even if its performing well i dont want to be greedy and increase more the Price Target.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;IRTC&lt;/strong&gt;: Price target: 288 max - 170 min EPS growth: Positive.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Bought 60 stocks at 175. 21 Leverage x1 Atm -2.35%&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Bought 10 stocks at 171.18 Leverage x5 Atm +2.4%&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Take Profit at price target 185 (previous 200) Its resisting alot in this price thats why i decided to set close profit lower.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;LUMN&lt;/strong&gt;: Still Cautious (Not anymore this is going well) Price Target: max 17 - min 9 EPS: Low - Maybe in future it has some ptential to increase a little&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Bought last time 10 stocks at 11.77 Leverage x2 Atm: +0% (LOL THAT WAS CLOSE ) &lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Bought 50 stocks at 11.53 Leverage x5 Atm: +10.4%&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Take Profit at price target of 13.8( Last was 13.5)&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;WELL&lt;/strong&gt;: This is my replacement for BBBY High Risk &amp;amp; High Gain, It look like a good stocks with improvements in previous period with so good stats like revenues, net income, eps etc. Because it hasn&amp;#39;t fully recovered from covid i want to get on the spike i belive it will happen in next week.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Bought 10 stocks at 63.04 Leverage x5 Atm: + 29.10% That was f****ng fast.&lt;br/&gt; &lt;strong&gt;POSITION CLOSED at 29.10%&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;br/&gt; &lt;strong&gt;Today Manually thats enough to get a nice amount fast, didnt want to get greedy and wait for more or to hit Take Profit Target.&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;del&gt;Take Profit at 68.5 (was thinking to put it on 68 but because of the sudden spike i made it +0.5 didn&amp;#39;t want to be greedy)&lt;/del&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;del&gt;Stop Loss at 60 but still monitoring it closely to manually close this one also.&lt;/del&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AYX&lt;/strong&gt;: This was and is so undervalued... I couldnt let the chance not to buy after the today&amp;#39;s dip. It&amp;#39;s potential it&amp;#39;s close to the first one EHTH but should do more DD on this one if i want to invest more than the half of my BBBY Gains.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Bought 6 stock&amp;#39;s at 117.48 Leverage x5 Atm +1.92% (Yesterday i was at -5% so i think i did well with this one, lets see how it goes, looking promising one)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Take profit at 134 ( This will be adjusted in the future because it has a nice potential, need to do some DD on this to adjust Take Profit not enough time because of my main job)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Stop Loss at 105&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;NEW INVESTEMNT BEFORE WEEKEND&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;&lt;strong&gt;AKAM&lt;/strong&gt;: This is a new undervalued asset, same as AYX, its less volatile with nice potential mid Range (Not a few days investement like WELL that closed in 2 days with 29.1% Gains) &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Price target: 175 max - 115 min - atm 101.59 EPS (Its unrevalued a total of 13,2%) the stock when down even if they anounced Top result (17% growth rate increase, 12% Increase in Sales) and positive reorganisation.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Bought 8 stocks at 101.73 Leverage x5 Atm: -0.88% &lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Take Profit at 115 (This will be Adjusted ofc in future because i strongly belive this strong has really potential in mid term for 130, but its a greedy call so i will think more about it an see how it goes)&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Stop Loss at 95 (Read some rumors that even if the price target is higher than the current price there could be more downfall on the price like 80 or 85, so i will be cautious with a high stop lose) &lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;I hope everyone rest this weekend, clear your minds from investments for a strong next week (This going to Short - Mid Range Investors and not Long Term Investors, you guys can keep doing everything you usually do)&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/user/eni1993&quot;&gt; /u/eni1993 &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/lilukl/mid_range_investemnt_weekend_update_expectations/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/lilukl/mid_range_investemnt_weekend_update_expectations/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t3_lilukl</id><link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/lilukl/mid_range_investemnt_weekend_update_expectations/" /><updated>2021-02-12T21:57:48+00:00</updated><title>Mid Range Investemnt Weekend Update &amp; Expectations - (I Will continue to do those DD every time i make changes in my orders)</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/SparkEthos</name><uri>https://www.reddit.com/user/SparkEthos</uri></author><category term="investing" label="r/investing"/><content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;While this sub mostly discusses trading in the stock market, many of us are also invested in the real estate market, so this article may interest you.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TL;DR&lt;/strong&gt;: Risks to real estate from increasing natural disaster frequency are not not priced in. Mechanics behind how risk is spread out could mean rapidly spreading economic harm.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Some of you may remember 2008, the tumult of the housing bubble, and subsequent collapse in prices. Today housing prices are again at an all time high, outpacing inflation in a similar fashion to 2008. This has many folks who have money in real estate on edge. However, there are significant differences between today&amp;#39;s market and that of 2008 in that the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.huduser.gov/portal/sites/default/files/pdf/NationalSummary_3Q20.pdf&quot;&gt;demand appears to be real and the supply constrains appear to be real&lt;/a&gt;. But I am always on the lookout for weakness in this space since the housing market accounted for &lt;a href=&quot;https://fas.org/sgp/crs/misc/IF11327.pdf&quot;&gt;15% of GDP in 2018&lt;/a&gt; (and is probably more in 2021). Weakness here tends to spread through the economy and affects all investments in one way or another.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Therefore, I present to you a very interesting threat to the housing market: &lt;strong&gt;climate change&lt;/strong&gt;. In the following Harvard Business Review interview with John Macomber (a senior lecture in Harvard Business School) he lays out this threat as manifesting itself through the insurance sector.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://hbr.org/2020/12/are-we-on-the-verge-of-another-financial-crisis&quot;&gt;https://hbr.org/2020/12/are-we-on-the-verge-of-another-financial-crisis&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;For those who don&amp;#39;t want to read the whole thing, I&amp;#39;ll summarize as best I can&lt;/strong&gt;: Climate change is rapidly increasing the rate of natural disasters from hurricanes to flooding to wild fires. Insurance premiums are yet to express this primarily due to government intervention (IE states providing disaster relief and mandates to insurers). The risks to real estate as an investment are increasing rapidly, yet society appears unaware and the market is not pricing this risk in. When state governments and the federal government realize they can no longer to afford to subsidize the rebuilding/repairs to homes there is risk of the system snapping as insurers go bottom up and premiums shoot through the roof.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;What&amp;#39;s more insurers are actually insured themselves by &amp;quot;re-insurers&amp;quot; (bet you never heard of them before right) who then slice off some of the risk by providing insurance-linked securities called &amp;quot;catastrophe bonds.&amp;quot; These are bought by investors who essentially get paid to take on some of the underlying risk. So the risk is spread out multiple steps away from the actual asset: your home. Sound familiar? This is eerily similar to the way mortgages were packaged and sold in the years leading up to 2008 (mortgage-backed securities). It is difficult to say how spread out and linked with the rest of the economy these catastrophe bonds are.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The fear is that housing prices are getting overinflated because the physical risk to the property are hidden from public view. Govt funds dry up. Insurers suddenly feel the full brunt of the increasing frequency of natural disasters. Premiums go sky high. Catastrophe bonds become worthless. Perceived wealth suddenly dries up and the contagion spreads through the whole economy. &lt;em&gt;Pop.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;There is more to the interview and if your interest is piqued I&amp;#39;ll let you read the rest, but this is the point I want to discuss with you all.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;My Take:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I was reminded about this hypothesis after Reuters did this article today about huge insurance rate hikes in Florida: &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-insurance-florida/florida-consumers-flabbergasted-as-property-insurers-push-for-double-digit-rate-hikes-idUSKBN2AC111&quot;&gt;https://www.reuters.com/article/us-usa-insurance-florida/florida-consumers-flabbergasted-as-property-insurers-push-for-double-digit-rate-hikes-idUSKBN2AC111&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Now, I&amp;#39;m no expert in real estate or insurance, I&amp;#39;m just a guy who owns some property. But like any investor I want to make sure my investment is worth the value its assigned and that potential risks are mitigated. What concerns me about this scenario is how the very real risks caused by climate change to real estate are &lt;em&gt;not being talked about in the public sphere&lt;/em&gt;. What else would climate change and the subsequent increase in natural disasters have a direct impact on except for real estate.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;It is really hard to say if this situation could actually lead to a massive collapse of the housing market and subsequent economic recession. As John Macomber states the ideal situation is that these risks become more apparent over time and the risks get priced in. If so, it would provide mainly a downward pressure on the real estate market rather than trigger a collapse. I actually think this is the more likely situation when the market is taken as a whole. Surely certain pockets will experience higher risk than others.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;I&amp;#39;m curious to hear your thoughts.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Edit: Added TL;DR&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/user/SparkEthos&quot;&gt; /u/SparkEthos &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/lijywx/a_threat_to_our_real_estate_investments_climate/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/lijywx/a_threat_to_our_real_estate_investments_climate/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t3_lijywx</id><link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/lijywx/a_threat_to_our_real_estate_investments_climate/" /><updated>2021-02-12T20:29:05+00:00</updated><title>A threat to our real estate investments: Climate Change and Insurance</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/spitfirestudios</name><uri>https://www.reddit.com/user/spitfirestudios</uri></author><category term="investing" label="r/investing"/><content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Just a question about options value .&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;So I&amp;#39;m aware that theta decay is the time value of an option and the closer you get to expiry the more the value of the option drops if it hasn&amp;#39;t met the stroke price yet.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;My question is are any of those losses permanent? I&amp;#39;ve found that my options tend to &amp;quot;step&amp;quot; down day on day and it doesn&amp;#39;t seem like it gets back to the same level as the day before even if the value of the stock I hold options on nears the strike price. Is this just the effect of the compounding of the averages of all of my call options that suffer theta decay?&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/user/spitfirestudios&quot;&gt; /u/spitfirestudios &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/lih0yd/theta_decay_options_and_value_stepdowns_day_over/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/lih0yd/theta_decay_options_and_value_stepdowns_day_over/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t3_lih0yd</id><link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/lih0yd/theta_decay_options_and_value_stepdowns_day_over/" /><updated>2021-02-12T18:16:16+00:00</updated><title>Theta decay, options and value step-downs day over day.</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/RipePetunia</name><uri>https://www.reddit.com/user/RipePetunia</uri></author><category term="investing" label="r/investing"/><content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Hear me out, I know this is EXTREMELY speculative.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Back in 2019 it was stated Canoo’s beta cars were produced “by an undisclosed contract manufacturer based in Michigan.” &lt;a href=&quot;https://techcrunch.com/2019/09/24/canoo-takes-the-covers-off-of-its-debut-electric-vehicle/&quot;&gt;https://techcrunch.com/2019/09/24/canoo-takes-the-covers-off-of-its-debut-electric-vehicle/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The only other location other than California where Canoo is hiring is the Dallas/Fort Worth area. &lt;a href=&quot;https://canoo.breezy.hr&quot;&gt;https://canoo.breezy.hr&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;GM has a manufacturing plant right next door in Arlington. &lt;a href=&quot;https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Arlington_Assembly&quot;&gt;https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Arlington_Assembly&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;GM announced 30 new EVs by 2025 in their super bowl commercial (skip to end). &lt;a href=&quot;https://youtu.be/mdsPvbSpB2Y&quot;&gt;https://youtu.be/mdsPvbSpB2Y&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;In their interview with Credit Suisse, (skip to around the 33:00 the good stuff) they state their plan to finalize their manufacturing partnership among other partnerships as well by Q2. &lt;a href=&quot;https://kvgo.com/credit-suisse/canoo-2020&quot;&gt;https://kvgo.com/credit-suisse/canoo-2020&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;BONUS TIN HAT LEVEL SPECULATION - GM will produce the power train for the Cruise Origin, whose platform looks similar to Canoo&amp;#39;s. The engine specs are still unreleased as well. Looking at their company website, getcruise.com, it seems like the business models of the two companies would be mutually beneficial. If they were to be involved in this, it could explain their talks with Apple falling through as it could possibly be a conflict of interest in bringing a level 5 AV to market. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.google.com/amp/s/www.theverge.com/platform/amp/2020/1/21/21075977/cruise-driverless-car-gm-no-steering-wheel-pedals-ev-exclusive-first-look&quot;&gt;https://www.google.com/amp/s/www.theverge.com/platform/amp/2020/1/21/21075977/cruise-driverless-car-gm-no-steering-wheel-pedals-ev-exclusive-first-look&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/user/RipePetunia&quot;&gt; /u/RipePetunia &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/limwto/canoo_may_have_something_cooking_with_gm/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/limwto/canoo_may_have_something_cooking_with_gm/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t3_limwto</id><link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/limwto/canoo_may_have_something_cooking_with_gm/" /><updated>2021-02-12T22:49:01+00:00</updated><title>Canoo may have something cooking with GM</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/diboy2</name><uri>https://www.reddit.com/user/diboy2</uri></author><category term="investing" label="r/investing"/><content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.marketwatch.com/story/disney-earnings-surge-in-disney-subscriptions-leads-to-surprise-profit-11613078561?siteid=yhoof2&quot;&gt;https://www.marketwatch.com/story/disney-earnings-surge-in-disney-subscriptions-leads-to-surprise-profit-11613078561?siteid=yhoof2&lt;/a&gt; &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“Disney+ has exceeded even our highest expectations,” Chapek said in a &lt;a href=&quot;https://edge.media-server.com/mmc/p/snvice4i&quot;&gt;conference call with analysts&lt;/a&gt; later, noting it stood at 26.5 million subscribers in the same-quarter a year ago. He also noted spikes in usage for ESPN+ (up 83% to 12.1 million) and Hulu (up 30% to 35.4 million).&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Disney’s Media and Entertainment Distribution, which includes Disney+, brought in $12.66 billion for the quarter, a decline of 5% from the same quarter a year ago before the pandemic swept across the country. The Disney Parks, Experiences and Products unit took in $3.6 billion, down 53% year-over-year as many Disney parks and its cruise line remain closed. The flagship Disneyland Park in Anaheim, Calif., and Disneyland Paris will stay closed in the current quarter, Disney Chief Financial Officer Christine McCarthy said during the analyst call.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The sustained strength of Disney+ has impressed Wall Street analysts despite stiffening competition from Apple Inc.’s &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.marketwatch.com/investing/stock/AAPL?mod=MW_story_quote&quot;&gt;AAPL&lt;/a&gt; Apple TV+, Netflix Inc. &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.marketwatch.com/investing/stock/NFLX?mod=MW_story_quote&quot;&gt;NFLX,&lt;/a&gt; AT&amp;amp;T Inc.’s &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.marketwatch.com/investing/stock/T?mod=MW_story_quote&quot;&gt;T&lt;/a&gt; HBO Max, Comcast Corp.’s &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.marketwatch.com/investing/stock/CMCSA?mod=MW_story_quote&quot;&gt;CMCSA&lt;/a&gt; Peacock, Amazon.com Inc.’s &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.marketwatch.com/investing/stock/AMZN?mod=MW_story_quote&quot;&gt;AMZN&lt;/a&gt; Prime Video, and others.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/user/diboy2&quot;&gt; /u/diboy2 &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/lhwg4r/surge_by_disney_to_nearly_95_million/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/lhwg4r/surge_by_disney_to_nearly_95_million/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t3_lhwg4r</id><link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/lhwg4r/surge_by_disney_to_nearly_95_million/" /><updated>2021-02-11T22:20:00+00:00</updated><title>Surge by Disney+ to nearly 95 million subscriptions leads to surprise profit</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/git_und_slotermeyer</name><uri>https://www.reddit.com/user/git_und_slotermeyer</uri></author><category term="investing" label="r/investing"/><content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://finance.yahoo.com/news/worst-stocks-are-doing-the-best-morning-brief-110238013.html?.tsrc=fin-notif&quot;&gt;https://finance.yahoo.com/news/worst-stocks-are-doing-the-best-morning-brief-110238013.html?.tsrc=fin-notif&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Any thoughts on this? The article states what I&amp;#39;m feeling for quite a while now. As an example, AstraZeneca published a doubling of their 2020 profit, meanwhile the stock&amp;#39;s average declines and it hardly moves on the news, as if real profit doesn&amp;#39;t matter any more. (I have no stake in AstraZeneca)&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/user/git_und_slotermeyer&quot;&gt; /u/git_und_slotermeyer &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/lhkjqr/the_worst_stocks_are_doing_the_best/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/lhkjqr/the_worst_stocks_are_doing_the_best/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t3_lhkjqr</id><link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/lhkjqr/the_worst_stocks_are_doing_the_best/" /><updated>2021-02-11T13:22:46+00:00</updated><title>&quot;The worst stocks are doing the best&quot;</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/Oni_Imports</name><uri>https://www.reddit.com/user/Oni_Imports</uri></author><category term="investing" label="r/investing"/><content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;CTHR (Charles &amp;amp; Colvard Jewelry) recently released their quarterly report and here&amp;#39;s the breakdown:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;- Highest Quarterly Revenue and Income from Operations in Company&amp;#39;s 25 Year History&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;- Revenue Growth of 14% Driven by 25% Increase in Online Channels&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;- Gross Margin Performance of 49%&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;- EPS Growth of 200% per Share from Year-Ago Quarter&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Other things they&amp;#39;ve been up to recently:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;ul&gt; &lt;li&gt;Expanded the product assortment of bridal and fine jewelry styles including engagement rings, wedding bands, earrings, necklaces and bracelets and launched personalized jewelry pieces set with Caydia™ lab grown diamonds.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Hosted a lab created gemstones workshop with more than 30 notable media editors.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Deployed awareness-building social media campaigns and marketing collaborations, that included Charles &amp;amp; Colvard jewelry being featured on the ABC network&amp;#39;s hit television series &lt;em&gt;The&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;Bachelorette&lt;/em&gt;;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Featured in multiple media articles from top digital publications, including &lt;em&gt;Forbes.com,&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;Yahoo.com&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Brides.com&lt;/em&gt;, The &lt;em&gt;Knot.com&lt;/em&gt; &lt;em&gt;and JCK;&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Presented at the LD Micro Virtual Investor Conference; and&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Net sales increased 14%, to $12.1 million for the quarter, compared with $10.7 million in the year-ago quarter.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Finished jewelry net sales increased 28% to $8.3 million for the quarter, compared to $6.4 million in the year-ago quarter.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Loose jewel net sales were $3.9 million for the quarter, a decrease of 8%, compared with $4.2 million in the year-ago quarter.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Operating expenses decreased 21% to $3.5 million for the quarter, compared to $4.4 million in the year-ago quarter.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;li&gt;Net income increased 209% to $2.5 million for the quarter, compared to net income of $814,000 in the year-ago quarter.&lt;/li&gt; &lt;/ul&gt; &lt;p&gt;Who they are and the market situation:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;CTHR is a US based jewelry company specializing in moissanite and synthetic lab grown diamonds. They&amp;#39;ve been around since 1995, but have only recently begun to grow with the growth of the synthetic diamond market.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The lab grown diamond industry is growing quickly, by 2030, the &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.statista.com/statistics/1078280/global-market-volume-of-lab-grown-diamonds/&quot;&gt;global market volume of lab-grown diamonds&lt;/a&gt; is forecast to be nearly 19.2 million carats, compared to its current 6.2 carats. The technology to produce synthetic diamonds is rapidly growing, it already takes mere weeks to produce from start to finish today.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;As a company that got a foot in the door early on (in my non-professional opinion) Charles and Colvard are in a fairly good position to continue to grow and maintain a solid holding in the new synthetic diamond industry over the next decade.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;TL;DR: If you&amp;#39;re wanting to get into the gemstone stock long haul, in my personal opinion, indicators look to point that CTHR should do fairly well over the next 10 years.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/user/Oni_Imports&quot;&gt; /u/Oni_Imports &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/lidpyc/in_honor_of_upcoming_valentines_day_lets_take_a/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/lidpyc/in_honor_of_upcoming_valentines_day_lets_take_a/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t3_lidpyc</id><link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/lidpyc/in_honor_of_upcoming_valentines_day_lets_take_a/" /><updated>2021-02-12T15:48:34+00:00</updated><title>In honor of upcoming Valentines Day, lets take a look at CTHR again</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/bragghy</name><uri>https://www.reddit.com/user/bragghy</uri></author><category term="investing" label="r/investing"/><content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;Ok guys, let&amp;#39;s throw away the year-old arguments about valuations and modelling and how TSLA&amp;#39;s price is 10-20x what it should be even not accounting for all the competition that it might have in the future.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;At this point the only key measure to look at here is &lt;strong&gt;market cap:&lt;/strong&gt; we are looking at a $768B company, almost $1T. In case you haven&amp;#39;t noticed, there aren&amp;#39;t a lot of companies thare are worth significantly more than that. Only AAPL, MSFT, AMZN and Saudi Aramco thare are worth more than double the price of TSLA, and they are all cash cows with massive amounts of actual real profits and fat margins, something that Elon Musk doesn&amp;#39;t have.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Even if TSLA stock rallied heavilyin the next months, it could as well double and go into the same league as those blue chips, but &lt;strong&gt;REALISTICALLY, it&amp;#39;s not a 10 bagger potential ANYMORE: do you actually believe that there would be LITERALLY TRILLIONS of dollars flowing into this stock?&lt;/strong&gt; Because to increase its price we need those numbers at this point.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Really think about the people that could buy TSLA at this point, basically everybody knows it&amp;#39;s a massive bubble, and it&amp;#39;s much easier to justify taking that massive risk if you know you could be in for a multibagger upside wise, but it&amp;#39;s not easy given the relatively small upside of today.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Having said all that, there needs to be a catalyst. In the next few years, as competiton in EV and autonomus driving space starts to thicken, we might finally see a meltdown ...&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;What do you guys think about this?&lt;/strong&gt; I might be wrong and many hedge fund legends have lost billions shorting this stuff, but at this point the poop smell is just too much. Burry shorted this a couple of months back, he predicted 2008, he predicted Game Stop, he might be right on this too.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The other interesting point is that if TSLA falls, it might take down the entire market with it, or at least a good portion of the NASDAQ&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/user/bragghy&quot;&gt; /u/bragghy &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/ligun1/the_incentive_to_short_tsla_is_just_massive_at/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/ligun1/the_incentive_to_short_tsla_is_just_massive_at/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t3_ligun1</id><link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/ligun1/the_incentive_to_short_tsla_is_just_massive_at/" /><updated>2021-02-12T18:08:51+00:00</updated><title>The incentive to short TSLA is just massive at this point</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/flynick</name><uri>https://www.reddit.com/user/flynick</uri></author><category term="investing" label="r/investing"/><content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;To anyone looking for a great play that&amp;#39;s been quietly flying under the radar, let me introduce you to one of the best SPACs this year that&amp;#39;s barely being talked about.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Apex Technologies / AvePoint Inc.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;In November of 2020 AvePoint, the largest Microsoft 365 Data Management Solutions Provider announced a $2B merger with Apex Technologies. The deal is expected to close this quarter and AvePoint will begin trading under the new ticker AVPT.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Why is this one of the most undervalued SPACs right now?&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;1.) All Star Leadership&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Both Apex and AvePoint boast great leadership teams. At Apex, Jeff Epstein (lol), serves as the co-CEO and CFO. Jeff has held board/executive positions at companies such as Oracle, Twilio, Nielsen, Booking Holdings among others. The other co-CEO, Brad Koenig has served as the Global Head of Technology Investment Banking at Goldman Sachs for 15+ years and has served clients such as Dell, eBay, Microsoft, SAP, Veritas, Oracle in advisory capacities. Both Jeff and Brad will join the board of AvePoint once the merger goes through.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The current CEO of AvePoint Tianyi Jang, who&amp;#39;s 23 years in the industry include positions at Deutsche, Lehman Brothers, and Citadel will remain as the CEO. The rest of the executive team boast past positions at companies such as Deloitte, Johnson &amp;amp; Johnson, Verizon, Merril Lynch and many others.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;2.) Total Addressable Market&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;We all know how huge cloud computing is and will continue to be through the future. This is no new news. AvePoint estimates their TAM to grow to over $33B by 2022. As a strategic cloud partner of Microsoft and a 5x Global Partner of the Year Recipient, they&amp;#39;re very well positioned to grow along side Microsoft and the cloud computing space as a whole. This growth is only being accelerated by the pandemic.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.gartner.com/en/newsroom/press-releases/2020-07-23-gartner-forecasts-worldwide-public-cloud-revenue-to-grow-6point3-percent-in-2020&quot;&gt;https://www.gartner.com/en/newsroom/press-releases/2020-07-23-gartner-forecasts-worldwide-public-cloud-revenue-to-grow-6point3-percent-in-2020&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.pwc.com/us/en/industries/tmt/library/covid19-cloud-infrastructure.html&quot;&gt;https://www.pwc.com/us/en/industries/tmt/library/covid19-cloud-infrastructure.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;This partnership also allows a large competitive advantage as AvePoint offers the only full suite of SaaS solutions to migrate, manage, and secure data in Microsoft 365. Within the 7mm cloud users, previously mentioned there&amp;#39;s some blockbuster Fortune 500 companies relying on AvePoint&amp;#39;s technology everyday.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://imgur.com/a/0AjhMOp&quot;&gt;https://imgur.com/a/0AjhMOp&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;3.) Financials and Growth&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Full Year Total Revenue for 2020 closed somewhere between $148M and $151M, up 29% year over Year. Cash, Cash Equivalents, and Short Term Investments total approximately $70M as of December 30, 2020 with a ~14% EBIT margin. The company also remains completely debt-free.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://currently.att.yahoo.com/att/apex-technology-acquisition-corporation-avepoint-120000775.html?guccounter=1&amp;amp;guce_referrer=aHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuZ29vZ2xlLmNvbS8&amp;amp;guce_referrer_sig=AQAAAAJkj9TMthTRpFA4YOKfMXxTJ32_2uIMtn7tqMm5C5AurJm-1jnzqJ8A8u0__GoF71BAC5EIV1TIIcXAZh-jvBC4gdkY0dRBSeAEt46s6XHCyl16vrAhUtkaNwF1JA5Df0kGvKHP-ZxQLlDnqfgPVF_L-UckoGdw4JWb6NlwU3t7&quot;&gt;https://currently.att.yahoo.com/att/apex-technology-acquisition-corporation-avepoint-120000775.html?guccounter=1&amp;amp;guce_referrer=aHR0cHM6Ly93d3cuZ29vZ2xlLmNvbS8&amp;amp;guce_referrer_sig=AQAAAAJkj9TMthTRpFA4YOKfMXxTJ32_2uIMtn7tqMm5C5AurJm-1jnzqJ8A8u0__GoF71BAC5EIV1TIIcXAZh-jvBC4gdkY0dRBSeAEt46s6XHCyl16vrAhUtkaNwF1JA5Df0kGvKHP-ZxQLlDnqfgPVF_L-UckoGdw4JWb6NlwU3t7&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;With an additional $252mm in cash on its balance sheet from the transaction, there will be plenty of room to grow. Some of the avenues AvePoint plans attacking include; selling more to existing customers, increasing SMB footprint, capturing a larger share of the Microsoft Cloud Customer Base (currently only 3% with no meaningful competition in the space), and expanding target industry focus and international targets.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Been holding 200 shares since late November and am shocked this merger isn&amp;#39;t getting more attention. In the year of the SPAC, this one stands out as one of the best. I see at as a great simultaneous growth and value play and wanted to share. Cheers.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Additional Financials:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://imgur.com/a/V1jZU2r&quot;&gt;https://imgur.com/a/V1jZU2r&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://imgur.com/a/QQ5A3S6&quot;&gt;https://imgur.com/a/QQ5A3S6&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Main Sources:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://cdn.avepoint.com/pdfs/en/Apex-AvePoint%20Investor%20Presentation_Webcast_Final%20(11.23.2020&quot;&gt;https://cdn.avepoint.com/pdfs/en/Apex-AvePoint%20Investor%20Presentation_Webcast_Final%20(11.23.2020).pdf&lt;/a&gt;.pdf)&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.sec.gov/cgi-bin/browse-edgar?CIK=1777921&amp;amp;owner=exclude&quot;&gt;https://www.sec.gov/cgi-bin/browse-edgar?CIK=1777921&amp;amp;owner=exclude&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/user/flynick&quot;&gt; /u/flynick &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/li2hfz/apxt_the_dark_horse_spac/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/li2hfz/apxt_the_dark_horse_spac/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t3_li2hfz</id><link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/li2hfz/apxt_the_dark_horse_spac/" /><updated>2021-02-12T03:23:35+00:00</updated><title>APXT - The Dark Horse SPAC</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/captain_holt_nypd</name><uri>https://www.reddit.com/user/captain_holt_nypd</uri></author><category term="investing" label="r/investing"/><content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;$FSR is an EV company that engages in researching, developing, and producing next-generation electrically powered vehicles.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;5 hours ago, Morgan Stanley set a PT of $27 for $FSR:&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://thefly.com/landingPageNews.php?id=3246514&amp;amp;headline=FSR-Fisker-initiated-with-an-Overweight-at-Morgan-Stanley&quot;&gt;https://thefly.com/landingPageNews.php?id=3246514&amp;amp;headline=FSR-Fisker-initiated-with-an-Overweight-at-Morgan-Stanley&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Since the report, it has risen 8.74% in the after-hours, putting it at $16.79. That&amp;#39;s a 60% potential gain at a PT of $27.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;This stock ran to $23 in November off a $26 pt from Credit Suisse. A couple $15-16 targets sent this into a long accumulation range that its finally ready to break out of.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Fisker has failed previously with car companies specifically, so why is it different this time?&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Henrik Fisker owns patents on solid-state battery tech and teased class-leading range in a call at the Goldman Sachs conference today&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://insideevs.com/news/336654/fisker-patents-solid-state-battery-tech-commercialization-by-2023/amp/&quot;&gt;https://insideevs.com/news/336654/fisker-patents-solid-state-battery-tech-commercialization-by-2023/amp/&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Magna is their manufacturing partner and owns a 6% stake as part of the deal&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.cnbc.com/amp/2020/10/15/fisker-closes-deal-for-supplier-magna-to-build-its-ocean-electric-suv.html&quot;&gt;https://www.cnbc.com/amp/2020/10/15/fisker-closes-deal-for-supplier-magna-to-build-its-ocean-electric-suv.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Besides Morgan Stanley, other analysts and research groups have almost unanimously put $FSK as a &amp;quot;buy&amp;quot; and a price target well above its current price.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Other equities research analysts also recently issued research reports about the stock. Citigroup Inc. 3% Minimum Coupon Principal Protected Based Upon Russell initiated coverage on shares of Fisker in a research note on Wednesday, November 25th. They set a “buy” rating and a $26.00 price target on the stock. Smith Barney Citigroup began coverage on shares of Fisker in a research note on Wednesday, November 25th. They issued a “buy” rating and a $26.00 target price on the stock. Wolfe Research began coverage on shares of Fisker in a research note on Wednesday, December 9th. They issued an “underperform” rating and a $16.00 target price on the stock. Vertical Research began coverage on shares of Fisker in a research note on Monday, January 4th. They issued a “buy” rating on the stock. Finally, Raymond James began coverage on shares of Fisker in a research report on Thursday, January 21st. They set a “market perform” rating on the stock. One research analyst has rated the stock with a sell rating, two have assigned a hold rating and five have assigned a buy rating to the company. The company presently has a consensus rating of “Buy” and a consensus price target of $21.00.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.americanbankingnews.com/2021/02/11/fisker-nysefsr-coverage-initiated-at-morgan-stanley.html&quot;&gt;https://www.americanbankingnews.com/2021/02/11/fisker-nysefsr-coverage-initiated-at-morgan-stanley.html&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Do I think it&amp;#39;s a great long term hold? No. But the Morgan Stanley valuation alone is a big enough hype to raise the price well above $20 in the short term according to my research.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Positions: $FSR 3 contracts $18.5c 3/5&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/user/captain_holt_nypd&quot;&gt; /u/captain_holt_nypd &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/li2o55/fsr_60_potential_gain_27_pt_morgan_stanley_dd/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/li2o55/fsr_60_potential_gain_27_pt_morgan_stanley_dd/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t3_li2o55</id><link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/li2o55/fsr_60_potential_gain_27_pt_morgan_stanley_dd/" /><updated>2021-02-12T03:33:27+00:00</updated><title>$FSR - 60% potential gain $27 PT Morgan Stanley - DD</title></entry><entry><author><name>/u/buddhist-truth</name><uri>https://www.reddit.com/user/buddhist-truth</uri></author><category term="investing" label="r/investing"/><content type="html">&lt;!-- SC_OFF --&gt;&lt;div class=&quot;md&quot;&gt;&lt;p&gt;The first bitcoin exchange-traded fund (ETF) in North America has been given the go-ahead by Canada’s financial regulator.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;According to a decision document on Thursday, the receipt of approval from the Ontario Securities Commission was filed under a Multilateral Instrument passport system in multiple Canadian jurisdictions.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Those territories include British Columbia, Alberta, Saskatchewan, Manitoba, Quebec, New Brunswick, Nova Scotia, Prince Edward Island, Newfoundland and Labrador, Northwest Territories, Yukon and Nunavut.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;This story is developing and will be added to accordingly.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Update : WILL TRADE ON TSX &lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;TRUSTEE &amp;amp; PM: PurposeInvest&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;CUSTODIAN: CIDEL TRUST, Gemini (SUB-C)&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;BTC INDEX: TRADEBLOCK XBX&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;AUDITOR: EYnews&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;MGT FEES: 1% AVG DAILY NAV&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Ticket symbol : BTCC&lt;/p&gt; &lt;h2&gt;Update 2 (2/12) &lt;/h2&gt; &lt;p&gt;In the United States, more than 10 investment companies have filed with the Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) for similar products. Last month, President Joe Biden appointed a new SEC chair, prompting hopes that a bitcoin ETF could be approved in 2021.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;The OSC’s approval of BTCC could nudge other markets to see similar products come to light.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;“The SEC will definitely feel the pressure to allow such a product to come to the marketplace because there are already products in the market that are taking advantage of the exposure of bitcoin that are not efficient for investors and are not being done in a regulated format like the SEC would want,” he said.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;Bitcoin holdings are kept in “cold storage” – an offline custodian that cannot be hacked. Gemini Trust Company LLC will be sub-custodian for the fund, and CIBC Mellon Global Securities Services Co. will act as fund administrator.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;p&gt;BTCC has a 1 per cent management fee, and will invest in the physical form of bitcoin rather than futures that would allow investors to speculate on the price at a later date. The fund will track the TradeBlock XBX Index, which uses an algorithm to calculate the consolidated price of bitcoin every second.&lt;/p&gt; &lt;/div&gt;&lt;!-- SC_ON --&gt; &amp;#32; submitted by &amp;#32; &lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/user/buddhist-truth&quot;&gt; /u/buddhist-truth &lt;/a&gt; &lt;br/&gt; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/lhzl35/first_north_american_publicly_traded_bitcoin_etf/&quot;&gt;[link]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt; &amp;#32; &lt;span&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/lhzl35/first_north_american_publicly_traded_bitcoin_etf/&quot;&gt;[comments]&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/span&gt;</content><id>t3_lhzl35</id><link href="https://www.reddit.com/r/investing/comments/lhzl35/first_north_american_publicly_traded_bitcoin_etf/" /><updated>2021-02-12T00:49:38+00:00</updated><title>First North American Publicly traded Bitcoin ETF Approved by Canadian Securities Regulator</title></entry></feed>